http://www.recordstore.co.uk/privacy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out the basis on which any information (which may
include personal data, as defined in data protection law) we collect from you,
or that you provide to us, through this website, application or service (the
"Site") will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully
to understand our practices regarding your information and how we will treat
it.
Please click on the sections below to learn more about our privacy policy:
Cookies
Social media and other third parties that provide content, advertising or
Who we are
This site is operated by Digital Stores (a trading name of Universal Music Direct Limited), 4 Pancras Square, London N1C 4AG, Data Protection Number Z788930X
("We"), who is a data controller responsible for the processing of
personal data under applicable data protection law. We may share your personal
data with UMG Recordings Services Inc, of 2220 Colorado Avenue, Santa Monica,
California, USA, as an independent data controller under applicable data
protection law. Each of Universal Music Direct Limited and UMG Recordings
Services Inc. separately make the disclosures in this Privacy Policy to you
(and, where necessary, references in this Privacy Policy to "UMG" or
"we" will be deemed to be references to both entities for such
purpose).
As used in this Privacy Policy, "UMG Companies" includes all
entities UMG controls, is controlled by or is under common control with,
including subsidiaries, joint ventures or other entities in whom UMG has a
substantial ownership interest.
Contact
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed by
contacting UMG’s Data Protection Officer by filling in a
Privacy Office Inquiry Form
or by email at
privacy.officer@umusic.com.
For questions, comments or requests not related to this privacy policy please
see
Universal Music's FAQ
regarding how to contact UMG.
Information we may collect from you
When you use the Site or contact us by e-mail, social media, SMS, telephone,
or other methods, we may collect and process the following data about you:
Information you give us, including:
Forms filled out by you on the Site;
Content of correspondence with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise;
Site registration;
Subscriptions or orders placed on the Site;
Participation in discussion boards or other social media functions on
the Site;
Entering a competition, promotion or survey;
If applicable, resume, work history, CV, resume or other job application
information;
Reporting a problem or requesting support for the Site.
The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address
and phone number, date of birth, payment information, personal
description, photographs or images or comments.
Information we collect about you.
With regard to each of your visits to our Site we may automatically
collect the following information:
Technical information, including IP address, login information, browser
type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions,
operating system and platform;
Information about your visit, including the full URL clickstream to,
through and from our Site (including date and time); * Pages you viewed
or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits
to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling,
clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.
We may also collect information our about your devices (including phones,
computers or other devices) where you access and visit our Sites. Such
information may include unique device identifiers and mobile network
information (including phone number), IP address, language and time zone,
operating system, hardware version, device locations (including specific
geographic locations, such as through GPS, Bluetooth or WiFi signals).
Information we collect from other sources
We also work with third parties (including, for example, business partners,
sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising
networks, analytics providers, social networks such as Facebook and Twitter,
search information providers, credit reference agencies, third parties who
enable sign on functionality and social network integration) and may receive
information about you from them.
If you choose to use features on this Site or other UMG websites that connect
to your online profiles, accounts or services (including social media
accounts) (“Connected Accounts”), we may collect any information that you
permit through your settings on those Connected Accounts. For example, if you
log in to our site using your Facebook account and choose to allow Facebook to
share your profile with us, we may collect that information. Information we
receive from Connected Accounts includes email address, first and last name,
location (hometown and country), gender, date of birth, likes, posts or other
social activity. Please review your Connected Account privacy settings to
control what information is provided to us through this option.
If you are applying for a job at UMG, we may use information you provide to
communicate with third parties regarding your application to the extent
permissible by law, including to verify your credentials, work history,
references, conduct background checks, or other job application-related
purposes.
How your information may be used
We may use information held about you in the following ways:
To help us respond to your queries;
To provide you with information on the relevant Universal Music artist;
To provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with
information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to
those that you have already purchased or enquired about or that we feel may
interest you;
To make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our Site
about goods or services that may interest you or them;
To provide or permit third parties to provide targeted advertising via
websites you visit about goods or services that you may find interesting
(see more on this in our Cookies Policy below;
To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you
and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
To track the progress and number of entries in competitions and promotions.
To allow you to interact with our Site, for example by posting comments or
to share information from our Site on third party social media platforms;
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between
you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services
that you request from us;
To manage your access to the services or notify you about changes to the
services;
To comply with legal and regulatory requirements;
To administer our Site and for internal operations, including
troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey
purposes;
To improve our Site to ensure that content is presented in the most
effective manner for you and for your computer;
As part of our efforts to keep our Site safe and secure;
If you have applied for a job at UMG, to review, verify, and evaluate your
job application information.
We may combine information we receive from other sources with information you
give to us and information we collect about you (including information in
relation to your devices). We may use this combined information for the
purposes set out above.
For clarity, if you are a UMG artist, and the Site pertains to royalty
payments and your commercial relationship with UMG, then UMG shall only use
your information collected from such Site to facilitate royalty payments and
UMG’s management of its commercial relationship with you and as otherwise as
agreed in your artist agreement with UMG.
Disclosure of your information
We may share your personal data with
any UMG Company
and with selected third parties including:
Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any
contract we enter into with them or you in order to provide you with a
product or service;
Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors to provide you with
information about promotions and offers;
Relevant Universal Music artists and/or their representatives;
Advertisers, advertising networks and social networks that require the data
to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We may also use
aggregate and other information to help advertisers reach the kind of
audience they want to target. We may make use of the personal data we have
collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by
displaying their advertisement to that target audience;
Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and
optimisation of our Site;
Third parties when you consent to or request such sharing.
We may disclose your personal data to third parties:
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we
may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such
business or assets;
If the UMG Company that controls this Site or substantially all of its
assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it
about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to
comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our
terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the
rights, property, or safety of UMG Companies, our customers, or others. This
includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for
the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction;
To any other third party where lawful.
Storage and transfer of data
All the information you provide may be processed and stored, transferred or
accessed by entities around the world as described in this policy. We will
take steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with
this Privacy Policy. We have put in place technical and organisational
procedures designed to safeguard the information we collected on this Site.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not
completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data,
we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any
transmission is at your own risk.
Cookies
Our Site uses cookies and other tracking technologies to distinguish you from
other users of our Site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience
when you browse our Site and also allows us to improve our Site. For detailed
information on the cookies and other technologies we use and the purposes for
which we use them see our
Cookies Policy.
Social media and other third parties that provide content, advertising or
functionality on our services
Some of the content, advertising and functionality on our Site may be provided
by third parties that are not affiliated with us. For example, you may have
the opportunity to log in to our Site using sign-in services such as Facebook
Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity
and provide you the option to share certain personal data with us. Services
like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your
activities on this Site to your profile page to share with others within your
network.
Third-party advertisers also may have a presence on our Sites. These and other
third parties may collect or receive certain information about your use of our
Sites, including through the use of cookies and other Internet technologies,
and this information may be collected over time and combined with information
collected across different websites and online services.
Some of these companies participate in industry-developed programs designed to
provide consumers choices about whether to receive targeted advertising.
Please visit the websites operated by the
Network Advertising Initiative,
Digital Advertising Alliance, and
European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance.
Children
This Site is not directed toward children (as defined by local law) nor does
UMG knowingly collect information from children (as defined by local law)
without parental consent except where in compliance with applicable laws.
Your rights
You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to object to or
request the restriction of processing of your personal data, and to request
access to, rectification, erasure, and portability of your own personal data
by contacting us as described in the Contact section.
We may require you to prove your identity with approved identification if you
request this information.
You may also be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to lodge a
complaint with a supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of
your personal data infringes applicable law.
You are responsible for keeping your information current and up-to-date. You
may update your information by contacting us as described in the
Contact section. We will retain your information for as
long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will
retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal
obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email
address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you
may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following
the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email
preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us as described
in the Contact section.
If you have applied for a job at UMG, you may have certain rights under your
local laws regarding your application or our evaluation. You may submit any
requests to exercise your rights as described in the
Contact section.
Your California privacy rights
California residents may opt out of having their personally identifiable
information shared with third parties for those third parties' direct
marketing purposes by contacting us as described in the
Contact section.
Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms. Some web browsers may transmit
“do-not-track” signals to the websites and other online services with which a
user communicates. There is no industry standard that governs what, if
anything, websites should do when they receive these signals. UMG currently
does not take action in response to these signals.
Links to third party websites
Our Site, our newsletters and other communications may, from time to time,
contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers
and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note
that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept
any responsibility or liability for these policies.
Changes to our privacy policy
Any material changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be
posted on this page prior to the change becoming effective and/or we will
notify you through the Site or, where appropriate, by e-mail. Please check
back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.
Users of sites in the European Economic Erea
This section of this Privacy Policy applies only if you use the Site from a
country that is a
Member State of the European Economic Area, and supplements the information in this Privacy Policy.
Legal Basis for Data Processing: We process personal data for
the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, as described above. Our legal
basis to process personal data includes processing that is: necessary for the
performance of the contract between you and us (for example, to provide you
with the services you request and to identify and authenticate you so you may
use the Site); necessary to comply with legal requirements (for example, to
comply with applicable accounting rules and to make mandatory disclosures to
law enforcement); necessary for our legitimate interests (for example, to
manage our relationship with you and to improve the Site); and based on
consent by our customers (for example, to communicate with you about our
products and services and provide you with marketing information), which may
subsequently be withdrawn at any time (by using preference settings in emails
or on our Sites, using our
Privacy Office Inquiry Form, or emailing us as set out in the Contact section)
without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its
withdrawal.
We may use automated decision making technologies, including profiling, to
support our data processing activities. Our automated decision making
capabilities include logic that attempts to identify artists, music,
communications, products, or offers that we believe may interest you. By using
this logic, it helps us personalize your interactions with UMG and UMG
artists. For you, this means that you may see online advertisements, direct
marketing communications (if you have subscribed), or other advertising or
marketing messages or special offers based on your activity on our Sites or
interactions with UMG Companies or our third party partners.
In some instances, you may be required to provide us with personal data for
processing as described above, in order for us to be able to provide you to
use all the features of the Site.
International transfers
Our sharing your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy, may
involve transferring your data outside the European Economic Area (EEA).
Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar
degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring, where required by law, at
least one of the following safeguards is implemented:
transferring personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an
adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission;
using specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give
personal data the same protection it has in Europe; or
transferring personal data to the United States to an entity if they are
part of the Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection
to personal data shared between the Europe and the US.
You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to request a copy of
relevant safeguards by contacting UMG as described in the
Contact section.
Effective Date: May 15, 2018
